<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FoodReuseApp</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="hint_message_text">Type a message&#8230;</string>
    <string name="error_empty_message">Please enter a message</string>
    <string name="error_message_failed">Failed to send your message</string>
    <string name="guide">

    </string>
    <string name="rb">
        A non-profit, food rescue organisation that bridges the gap between hunger and excess food. Started on 23rd December 2017 under the
        able mentorship of former Director General of Police, Maharashtra, Mr. D. Sivanandhan, we aim to eliminate hunger, malnutrition and
        food wastage, many meals at a time.\n\n
        The way our NGO functions is simple. We pick up excess food from weddings, events, hotels, cafeterias, housing societies and deliver it to
        thousands of hungry people who live in slums or on the footpath. We also deliver daily meals to kids of Drona Foundation, Dharavi and
        the relatives of cancer patients at Tata Memorial Hospital. Other than that, we distribute freshly cooked food and raw grains to our
        regular beneficiaries. The NGO has a dedicated helpline where we can be reached and our dedicated vans pick up the excess food and
        redistribute it promptly, thus ensuring that the quality of the food remains intact.
    </string>
    <string name="fi">
        Zomato Feeding India has a network of 24,500+ volunteers present across 100+ cities in India, and has served 33+ million (3.3+ Crore)
        meals to people in need. Our beneficiaries include and are not limited to - children, women, the elderly, specially-abled and migrant
        labourers.\n\n
        Through our five key programs and with the help of our volunteers - our Hunger Heroes, we redistribute surplus healthy meals to those
        who don’t have adequate or regular access to it.
    </string>
    <string name="trha">
        The Robin Hood Army is a volunteer based, zero-funds organization that works to get surplus food from restaurants and the community to
        serve less fortunate people.\n\n
        Our local chapters are run by friends and colleagues, who hope to create a difference in their own unique way. For example, restaurants
        in the neighbourhood Green Park, will contribute to the homeless of the locality, through volunteers who live in Green Park. Our “Robins”
        are largely students and young working professionals – everyone does this in their free time. The lesser fortunate sections of society we
        serve include homeless families, orphanages, patients from public hospitals, and old age homes.
    </string>
    <string name="ngo">Many NGOs and organizations for social change have mushroomed in India in the previous decade but very few have
        expanded on the basis of scale and the impact on the community.\n\n
        And considering the lack of transparency in transactions in our country, donations and sponsorships too are not easy to receive too.\n\n
        In spite of all these hurdles, there are a few NGOs that have made substantial social impact in India until now and we would like you
        to support them.
</string>
    <string name="p"><![CDATA[
    Chat Room Rules\n\n

    •	Rule 1: No spamming.\n\n
    \tBegin your conversations with a simple, “Hi”\n\n\n

    •	Rule 2: No personal attacks or harassment.\n\n
    \tNo attacks against someone’s race, religion, politics, sex, sexual orientation etc.\n\n
    \tNo acts of harassment of a violent or sexual nature\n\n\n

    •	Rule 3: Don\'t monopolize the conversation.\n\n
    \tPlease, try to engage in conversation with other people. The chat room is for everybody, it\’s not just about you\n\n\n

    •	Rule 4: No solicitation.\n\n
    \tDon\’t pimp your latest Blog, Drawing, T-Shirts, or whatever. That\’s rude\n\n\n

    •	Rule 5: Don\'t use the chat room for your personal business.\n\n\n

    •	Rule 6: Everything Else\n\n
    \tAnything not mentioned in one of the rules above, but that is still considered bad behavior.\n\n\n

    Follow the rules and everyone can enjoy a happy chat room experience.]]></string>
</resources>
